Discover

Login

Sign up

Privacy Policy
--------------

Podyssey Podcasts Inc., which owns Podyssey (“Podyssey,” “we,” “us,” or “our”), takes the private nature of your information very seriously. This policy regarding our privacy practices (the “Privacy Policy”) describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use Podyssey (the “Site”) and/or Podyssey’s other domains, products, advertising products, services, and/or content, including our iOS or Android SDKs (collectively with the Site, the “Services”). When you use the Services, you also consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy; please read it carefully.

### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of information gathered when you are using or accessing the Services.

### What We Collect and How We Use It

#### Account Information

When you create an account on the Services (an “Account”), we’ll ask you for information such as your username, password, and email address (“Account Information”). We may use Account Information, alone or together with other information, to enhance and improve the Services, such as by personalization.

#### Email Communications with Us

As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive email and other communications from us. Administrative communications relating to your Account (e.g., for purposes of Account recovery or password reset) are considered part of the Services and your Account, which you may not be able to opt-out from receiving. We also may send you other kinds of emails, which you can opt-out of either from your by using the “Opt-Out” link in the emails themselves.

#### User Content

By default, all sharing through the Services is public, and when you provide us with content it is published so that anyone can view it. Content published and shared publicly is accessible to everyone, including search engines, and you may lose any privacy rights you might have regarding that content. In addition, information shared publicly may be copied and shared throughout the Internet, including through actions or features native to the Services.

#### Financial Information

We will sometimes collect financial information, such as information related to your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). This happens when you decide to purchase a Paid Service. We do not, however, store that financial information; such information is stored by our payment processor (the “Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy (the Payment Processor may also have other terms, and you are responsible for locating and familiarizing yourself with those terms, as applicable). We do receive certain information from our Payment Processor: (1) a unique token that we connect with your Account to enable you to make further purchases using the information stored by our Payment Processor and (2) in certain cases, the last four digits of the credit card number associated with that token, so that we can prevent fraudulent transactions and identity theft.

#### Information Related to Use of the Services

We collect information about how people use the Services, including those with an Account. This type of information may be collected in our log files each time you interact with (i.e., make a request to) the Services. We use internal tools and third party applications and services (like Google Analytics) to collect and analyze this information. Some of this information may also be associated with the Internet Protocol Address (“IP Address”) used to access the Services; some may be connected with your Account; and some may only be collected and used in aggregate form (as a statistical measure that wouldn’t identify you or your Account). We may also collect your IP Address when you make a project or upload a sticker as a means of fighting spam, malware, identity theft and generally keeping our users safe.

#### Information Related to Your Web Browser or Mobile Device

We automatically receive and record information from your web browser or Mobile device when you interact with the Services, such as your browser or device type and version, what sort of device you are using, your operating system and version, your language preference, the website or service that referred you to the Services, the date and time of each request you make to the Services, your screen display information, and information from any cookies we have placed on your web browser (as described below).

#### Information Collected Using Cookies and Web Tags

Cookies are text files that may be sent to and saved by your web browser when you access a website; your web browser stores these cookies in a way associated with each website you visit, and you can generally see your cookies through your browser settings, depending on what browser you’re using. A web tag is code or a pixel embedded in a web page, or email, that allows Podyssey or a third party to see that you have looked at that page. We use cookies and web tags to enable our servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you use the Services, as described above in “Information Related to Use of the Services.” Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain information that personally identifies you, and we don’t combine the general information collected through cookies with other such information to tell us who you are. However, we do use cookies to identify that you have logged in, and that your web browser has accessed the Services, and we may associate that information with your Account if you have one. We may also store unique or near-unique identifiers that we associate with your Account in our cookies. This information, in turn, is sometimes used as described above in “Information Related to Use of the Services.” Most web browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your web browser) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways.

Some services that we use (including Third Party Services), such as Google Analytics, use web tags and may also place their own cookies on your browser, and individual blogs on our network may contain code that places their own cookies. We also run limited-time studies using web tags, sometimes with third parties, to, for example, measure the effectiveness of our advertising or email. Note that, unless otherwise disclosed, this Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

#### With Whom Your Information Is Shared

We never share information we receive from you unless: (a) we have your permission to share that information; (b) we have given you prior notice that the information will be shared, and with whom (such as in this Privacy Policy); or © that information is aggregate information or other information that does not identify you.

#### Information Shared with the Public Through the Services

As noted in “User Content” above, by default, content published through the Services and many actions you take on the Services are shared with the public. Because this kind of information can be seen by anyone and may be indexed by search engines (like Google Search), you should be careful about what you choose to disclose publicly and make sure it’s information you want to share with everyone.

####Information You Share with Third Party Services You may access Third Party Services through the Services, for example by clicking on externally-pointing links. You may also choose to share information that you provide to us, like blog posts, with those Third Party Services (for example, by sharing posts to Twitter or Facebook). This Privacy Policy only governs information we collect and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services’ privacy policies.

#### Information Shared with Our Agents in Order to Operate and Improve the Services

In some cases, we share information that we store (such as IP Addresses) with third parties, such as service providers, consultants, and other agents (“Agents”), for the purposes of operating, enhancing, and improving the Services, and developing new products and services. For example, we may share information with service providers in order to fight spam, and third-party consultants may have access to information in the process of improving our processes and technology. Agents with whom we share such information for these reasons are generally bound by confidentiality obligations and, unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use information we share with them beyond the scope and duration of what is necessary to assist us.

#### Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell business assets. In these transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

#### Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others

We believe in freedom of expression, and, to the extent reasonable, we try to protect our community from baseless legal demands. That said, we also reserve the right to access, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary, in our sole discretion, to (i) satisfy any law, regulation, legal process, governmental request, or governmental order, (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, trust and safety, or technical issues (including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of improving security and preventing fraud, spam, and malware), (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect the rights, property, health or safety of us, our users, any third parties or the public in general, including but not limited to situations involving possible violence, suicide, or self-harm.

#### Information We Share with Your Consent or at Your Request

If you ask us to release information that we have about your Account, we will do so if reasonable and not unduly burdensome.

#### Information Shared with Other Third Parties

We may share or disclose non-private information, Aggregate Information, or other non-personally identifying information with people and entities that we do business with.

#### The Security of Your Information

Your Account Information is protected by a password or through third party access (Facebook Login or Google Signin) for your privacy and security. We may enable additional security features in the future, like multi-factor authentication. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your Account and information by creating a unique, secure, and protected password and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account on the Services. We seek to protect your information (including your Account Information) to ensure that it is kept private; however, we can’t guarantee the security of any information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

#### What Information You Can Access

If you are a registered user, you can access most information associated with your Account by logging into the Services and checking your Account Settings page. Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.

#### How to Delete Your Account and What Happens When You Delete Your Account

If you want to delete your Account, you can do so by emailing us at info@podyssey.fm and providing proof of authority over the Account. What constitutes “proof of authority” will vary depending on the circumstances, but generally will require sufficient identifying information so that we can be confident you are the Account owner. Deleting your Account may not fully remove the content you have published from our systems, as caching of, backups of, copies of, or references to your Account Information may not be immediately removed.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, using the process for modifications set forth in our Terms of Service. Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

#### Where to Direct Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, send a detailed message to us at info@podyssey.fm

* ### Product
    
* ### Company
    
* ### Social

🎉 Join the #1 community of podcast lovers and never miss a great podcast.

Sign up
